Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/khoivn8071 (LinkedIn) khoispace.io.vn/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Edge Computing
Triton Inference Server
Depth Anything

Certifications

Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree Machine Learning Specialization Intermediate Python Data Scientist Python for Data Science and Al

Honors-Awards

Data-Centric Al Competition - Top 15 Zalo Al Challenges 2022 - Top 9

Khoi Vo Nguyen

Al Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

My experience is in computer vision. I have actively pursued knowledge through independent study, recognizing the potential advantages of formal education in this field. Despite the lack of formal instruction, I am a resourceful individual with a proven ability to identify and overcome challenges independently.

My website: https://khoispace.io.vn/ Github: https://github.com/vnk8071/

Experience

viAct
Al Engineer
March 2024 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Hong Kong SAR

FPT Software

1 year 6 months

Al Engineer

December 2022 - February 2024 (1 year 3 months)

Quy Nhơn, Binh Dinh, Vietnam

- Developed and maintained an Al Assistant that supported explaining legal issues for a Korean department of 50 users using LangChain and Azure OpenAl.
- Led customized search which led to a 75% improvement in the product's accuracy which has about 5 thousand requests per day.
- Achieved MVP robust pipeline for number plate detection and tracking to detect and recognize edge camera inputs using Yolov7 model, OCR, and tracking
- Developed and trained anomaly model for detecting anomalies in manufacturing using the Anomalib framework and ONNX.
- Acquired a comprehensive understanding of artificial intelligence concepts and skills, actively sharing technical expertise with team members and clients.

Al Camp

September 2022 - December 2022 (4 months)

Quy Nhơn, Binh Dinh, Vietnam

Training program with knowledge of OOP, Machine Learning, and Deep Learning to become a Fresher Al Engineer. Besides, experience the actual projects and the working process of FPT Software.

A2DS Inc.

1 year 8 months

Machine Learning Engineer November 2021 - February 2023 (1 year 4 months)

- Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam
- Oversaw implementation of Dry Eye disease diagnostic, demonstrating proficiency in managing the end-to-end process from data collection to web application deployment for end-users, particularly in hospital settings using Yolov5 and optimizing in C++.
- Built image labeling that helped doctors easily label in the hospital using Label Studio and Docker.
- Enhanced domain knowledge in eye disease through continuous learning and collaboration. Utilized Docker for efficient project packaging, AWS for seamless back-end deployment.

Machine Learning Engineer Intern July 2021 - October 2021 (4 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Here, I have more time to learn and practice skills related to the field of machine learning, more specifically, the process from research to the production of eye diagnostic technology.

Some skills and applications when I did an internship at A2DS Inc.:

- Improve code structure (Python programming)
- Working with the server, Linux operating system, and version control system
- Proficient in Gitlab, Docker, Streamlit API, Label Studio, Postman, and more.

Education

International University - VNU HCMC
Undergraduate, Bioengineering and Biomedical Engineering · (August 2018 - March 2023)

Central Training Academy - FPT Software

Al Camp, Al Engineer · (September 2022 - December 2022)